Kontakt

www.linkedin.com/in/ sabinehueckmann (LinkedIn)

Top-Kenntnisse

Public Relations
Unternehmenskommunikation
Social Media

Languages

Englisch Deutsch

Dr. Sabine Hückmann

CEO, Ketchum Germany

Region Stuttgart

Zusammenfassung

CEO@Ketchum Germany (Brandzeichen, Emanate and Ketchum Pleon) on a mission of delivering data-based strategies and creative programs for the whole range of Corporate and Marketing Communications. With 25+ years of professional expericence in consulting brands and businesses of all sizes, from Fortune 500 and Dax 30 to midsized and owner-led Enterprises as well as start-ups, in analytics, change communication, digital transformation, innovation, integrated communications, issues and crisis communications, media and message trainings, strategic communications counsel. Described as people-centric, inclusive and passionate, curious, eager for innovation and a lover of complicated stuff.

Berufserfahrung

Ketchum Germany Holding GmbH CEO (Chief Executive Officer) Februar 2018 - Present (4 Jahre 3 Monate) Stuttgart und Umgebung, Deutschland

Ketchum Pleon GmbH
21 Jahre 4 Monate
CIO (Chief Innovation Officer)
Juli 2016 - Present (5 Jahre 10 Monate)

Managing Partner Januar 2001 - Juni 2016 (15 Jahre 6 Monate) Stuttgart

Brodeur Kohtes & Klewes GmbH Office Head Juli 1998 - Dezember 2000 (2 Jahre 6 Monate) Stuttgart

Ausbildung

Julius-Maximilians-Universität Würzburg Diplom, Chemie